IKLIMA AZIZAH JANNAH

Depok, Indonesia | (+62)87887840110 | <u>iklimaazizahjannah@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/iklima-azizah-jannah/ | https://github.com/iklimaazjnnh

Summary

As a final year student at Indraprasta PGRI University, I gained valuable experience and knowledge in web development through project-based learning. I have strong skills in logical thinking, bug analysis and implementation. Additionally, I excel in a collaborative team environment, and I am open to expanding my skills by learning new things.

Work Experience

PT. Mitsubishi Electric Automotive Indonesia (MEAINA) – Cikarang, Indonesia Software Engineering - Internship

Aug 2023 – Okt 2023

- Developed new features for the desktop application, increasing user engagement by 20% post-launch.
- Improved application security, reducing security incidents by 15% within two months.
- Fixing application code by 20% and preventing the occurrence of bugs.
- Enhanced application performance by optimizing the database, resulting in a 20% faster query response time.

Project Experience

Online Shop Application - Shalu's Sweet Shop

Mar 2023 – Jun 2023

Web Developer

- Analyzing business and user requirements to comprehend project objectives.
- Implementing visual designs using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Developing business logic and functionality for an online shop using the PHP programming language.

Desktop Application - Sistem Informasi Pelayanan Kesehatan Berbasis Java Desktop Application Developer

Mar 2023 – May 2023

besktop Application Developer

- Analyzing the requirements for the desktop application to be developed.
- Designing the structure and architecture of the desktop application.
- Writing and implementing code using Java.
- Conducting software testing to ensure the proper functioning of the application.

Education

Universitas Indraprasta PGRI

2020 - Present

Majoring in Information Technology - GPA 3.80 in 7 semesters

Certification & Training

- Web Developer Program, PT. Hactivate Indonesia (Hacktiv8), Kampus Merdeka Batch 5, 2023
- Junior Web Developer, BNSP, VSGA BPPTIK Kementerian Kominfo, No.62019 2513 19783 2022

Skills

Technical Skill: PHP, Javascript, Visual Basic, Java, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Visual Studio Code,

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel

Languages : Fluent in Indonesia and Intermediate in English